{
    "id": "e45ca2db58554f86b6cb34d61181363a",
    "title": "Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This shade is ……………………….. than that shade?",
            "description": "Use a comparative form before than.",
            "answers": [
                "darker",
                "dark",
                "darkest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got any shades ………………………… than this?",
            "description": "Use a comparative form before than.",
            "answers": [
                "light",
                "lighter",
                "lightest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am the ……………………….. in my family.",
            "description": "We use the superlative to compare one thing with the whole group to which it belongs. ",
            "answers": [
                "short",
                "shortest",
                "shorter"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We must buy a ……………………….. car. This is not fast enough.",
            "description": "Faster is the comparative form of fast. ",
            "answers": [
                "fastest",
                "more fast",
                "faster"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the ……………………….. person I have ever known.",
            "description": "Funniest is the superlative form of funny. ",
            "answers": [
                "most funny",
                "funniest",
                "funnyest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can a cat be as ………………………… as a dog?",
            "description": "We use the structure as…as… to say that two people or things are equal.",
            "answers": [
                "faithful",
                "more faithful",
                "most faithful"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She spoke ………………………… than her opponent in the debate.",
            "description": "More confidently is the comparative form of confidently. ",
            "answers": [
                "confidentlier",
                "more confidently",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven’t reached the station yet. We need to walk ……………………….",
            "description": "When we are talking about physical distance farther and further are both possible. ",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the ………………………. price you are willing to take?",
            "description": "Least is the superlative form of little. ",
            "answers": [
                "least",
                "little",
                "last"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Lead is ………………………… than any other metal.",
            "description": "Heavier is the comparative form of heavy. ",
            "answers": [
                "heavyier",
                "more heavy",
                "heavier"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had run ………………………… you could have caught him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "faster",
                "fastest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ……………………….. than anybody I know.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stubborner",
                "more stubborn",
                "most stubborn"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}